export default [
    [{
        'question': 'Portland\'s name was decided by a coin toss.  After which city was it almost named?',
        'category': 'social',
        'level': 1,
        'answerA': 'Hanover',
        'answerB': 'Syracuse',
        'answerC': 'Manchester',
        'answerD': 'Boston',
        'correctAnswer': 'D',
        score: 100
    },
    {
        'question': 'Portland\'s smallest park comes in at 2.5 feet in diameter.  What\'s its name?',
        'category': 'landmarks',
        'level': 2,
        'answerA': 'Director Park',
        'answerB': 'Mill Ends Park',
        'answerC': 'O\'Bryant Square',
        'answerD': 'Dawson Park',
        'correctAnswer': 'B',
        score: 100
    },
    {
        'question': 'At which Portland food establishment can you also get married?',
        'category': 'culture',
        'level': 1,
        'answerA': 'Jake\'s Famous Crawfish Seafood Restaurant',
        'answerB': 'Voodoo Donuts',
        'answerC': 'Laughing Planet',
        'answerD': 'Portland City Grill',
        'correctAnswer': 'B',
        score: 300
    },
    {
        'question': 'Which supernatural TV series was filmed in Portland?',
        'category': 'social',
        'level': 1,
        'answerA': 'Grimm',
        'answerB': 'Supernatural',
        'answerC': 'True Blood',
        'answerD': 'Sense8',
        'correctAnswer': 'A',
        score: 200
    },
    {
        'question': 'What neighborhood in Portland is at odds with the rectilinear grid followed by the rest of the city?',
        'category': 'landmarks',
        'level': 1,
        'answerA': 'Sunnyside',
        'answerB': 'Laurelhurst',
        'answerC': 'Ladd\'s Addition',
        'answerD': 'Irvington',
        'correctAnswer': 'C',
        score: 300
    },
    {
        'question': 'What month long festival each June celebrates bikes?',
        'category': 'culture',
        'level': 1,
        'answerA': 'Cyclepalooza',
        'answerB': 'Bikers Unite',
        'answerC': 'Pedalpalooza',
        'answerD': 'Bike Fest',
        'correctAnswer': 'C',
        score: 100
    },   
    {
        'question': 'What NPR host and Portland native occasionally tours with Pink Martini?',
        'category': 'social',
        'level': 1,
        'answerA': 'Audie Cornish',
        'answerB': 'Scott Simon',
        'answerC': 'Ari Shapiro',
        'answerD': 'Terry Gross',
        'correctAnswer': 'C',
        score: 300
    },
    {
        'question': 'What extinct volcano lies within the Portland city limits?',
        'category': 'landmarks',
        'level': 1,
        'answerA': 'Mt. Tabor',
        'answerB': 'Rocky Butte',
        'answerC': 'Powell Butte',
        'answerD': 'Kelly Butte',
        'correctAnswer': 'A',
        score: 200
    },
    {
        'question': 'Portland loves its coffee.  Per capita, in which area does it lead the nation?',
        'category': 'culture',
        'level': 1,
        'answerA': 'coffee roasters',
        'answerB': 'coffee shops',
        'answerC': 'baristas',
        'answerD': 'carts',
        score: 200   
    }],

    [{
        'question': 'What Portland establishment includes a 21 foot chocolate waterfall?',
        'category': 'landmarks',
        'level': 2,
        'answerA': 'Moonstruck',
        'answerB': 'Woodblock',
        'answerC': 'The Candy Basket',
        'answerD': 'Cacao',
        'correctAnswer': 'C',
        score: 400
    },
    {
        'question': 'Since 1912 these water fountains have provided free water to thirsty Portlanders.  They are?',
        'category': 'landmarks',
        'level': 3,
        'answerA': 'Lovejoy Fountains',
        'answerB': 'Failing Fountains',
        'answerC': 'Overton Bubblers',
        'answerD': 'Benson Bubblers',
        'correctAnswer': 'D',
        score: 500
    },
    {
        'question': 'The White Stag sign on the Willamette River initially advertised what?',
        'category': 'landmarks',
        'level': 2,
        'answerA': 'sugar',
        'answerB': 'flour',
        'answerC': 'salt',
        'answerD': 'clothing',
        'correctAnswer': 'A',
        score: 600
    },
    {
        'question': 'What Portland author won the Hugo, Nebula, Locus and World Fantasy Awards?',
        'category': 'social',
        'level': '2',
        'answerA': 'Jean Auel',
        'answerB': 'Arthur C. Clarke',
        'answerC': 'Orson Scott Card',
        'answerD': 'Ursula LeGuin',
        'correctAnswer': 'D',
        score: 700
    },
    {

    },
    {
        'question': 'What Portland singer competed on the television show "Rock Star Supernova"?',
        'category': 'social',
        'level': 2,
        'answerA': 'James Mercer',
        'answerB': 'Storm Large',
        'answerC': 'China Forbes',
        'answerD': 'Elliott Smith',
        'correctAnswer': 'B',
        score: 500
    }],

    [{
        'question': 'The oldest vehicular bridge across the Willamette River is the?',
        'category': 'landmarks',
        'level': 3,
        'answerA': 'Burnside Bridge',
        'answerB': 'Morrison Bridge',
        'answerC': 'Hawthorne Bridge',
        'answerD': 'Sellwood Bridge',
        'correctAnswer': 'C',
        score: 700
    },
    {
        'question': 'What statue is Portland is the second largest hammered copper sculpture in the US behind the Statue of Liberty?',
        'category': 'landmarks',
        'level': 3,
        'answerA': 'Portlandia',
        'answerB': 'Joan of Arc',
        'answerC': 'Sacajawea and Jean-Baptiste',
        'answerD': 'The Dream',
        'correctAnswer': 'A',
        score: 800
    },
    {
        'question': 'Why do the downtown streets on either side of Burnside come in at different angles?',
        'category': 'landmarks',
        'level': 3,
        'answerA': 'The river curves and the streets are parallel to the river.',
        'answerB': 'Downtown was platted on magnetic north and the Pearl on true north.',
        'answerC': 'There was no overall plan for the city.',
        'answerD': 'Both neighborhoods were already in existence and grew into each other.',
        'correctAnswer': 'B',
        score: 900
    }]
];